<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-03-31T23:45:34+02:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Zhang Zhan</title><entry><title type="html">Digital Design for the Central Registrar’s Office of Turin (ongoing)</title><link href="/2019/02/28/degital-design-for-the-central-registrars-office-of-turin.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Digital Design for the Central Registrar's Office of Turin (ongoing)" /><published>2019-02-28T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2019-02-28T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/2019/02/28/degital-design-for-the-central-registrars-office-of-turin</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/02/28/degital-design-for-the-central-registrars-office-of-turin.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Digital Design for the Central Registrar’s Office of Turin&lt;/em&gt; is a group project of a semsester-long design studio course of the master program of Digital and Interaction Design, at Politecnico di Milano. I am in the team with Alessandro Ceriani, Malte Simon Christensen, Sarah Anna Melanie Kraanen, and Irina Nikulina.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Italian bureaucrats would appear to love red tape and have invented official papers and stamps for every possible occasion and purpose. Just finding the right office is a challenge and when you finally locate it, it’s invariably closed (many offices open on a few days per week for a couple of hours only). You even need documents to obtain other documents and the laws governing the issue and use of these documents are frequently incomprehensible.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether being a stereotype or not, this paragraph from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.justlanded.com/english/Italy/Italy-Guide/Visas-Permits/Bureaucracy&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;one of the “Italy Guides”&lt;/a&gt; adequately summarizes outsiders’ views on and general reputation of Italian bureaucrats. With the unique yet extremely fundamental function, the Central Registrar’s Office of Turin is not an exception—long wait, insufficiency, chaos, incomprehensibility are what visitors are going through when they visit the site. The overall experience seems simply painful. With the trend of improving citizen’s overall experience within public sectors by implementing digitization around the world, the Central Registrar’s Office of Turin is definitely falling behind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this project, we begin with context analysis to identify user’s and employee’s needs and allocate touchpoints. Then we rely on User Centred Design approach based on a process of design-evaluation-redesign of the digital touchpoints of the Central Registrar’s Office of Turin. They are followed by development and implementation. In the project’s final piloting and integration phase, we test the developed services with a pilot and integrating them with the existing systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-15.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-16.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-17.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-18.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-19.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-20.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-21.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-22.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-23.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-24.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-25.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-26.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-27.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-28.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-29.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-30.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-31.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-32.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-33.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-34.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-35.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-36.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-37.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="design" /><summary type="html">Digital Design for the Central Registrar’s Office of Turin is a group project of a semsester-long design studio course of the master program of Digital and Interaction Design, at Politecnico di Milano. I am in the team with Alessandro Ceriani, Malte Simon Christensen, Sarah Anna Melanie Kraanen, and Irina Nikulina. “Italian bureaucrats would appear to love red tape and have invented official papers and stamps for every possible occasion and purpose. Just finding the right office is a challenge and when you finally locate it, it’s invariably closed (many offices open on a few days per week for a couple of hours only). You even need documents to obtain other documents and the laws governing the issue and use of these documents are frequently incomprehensible.”</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/digital-design-turin-featured-image.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Scalo Farini - Temporary Urban Tactics</title><link href="/2018/09/20/scalo-farini-temporary-urban-tactics.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Scalo Farini - Temporary Urban Tactics" /><published>2018-09-20T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2018-09-20T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>/2018/09/20/scalo-farini-temporary-urban-tactics</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/09/20/scalo-farini-temporary-urban-tactics.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-15.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-16.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-17.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-18.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-19.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-20.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-21.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-22.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-23.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-24.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-25.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-26.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-27.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-28.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-29.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-30.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-31.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-32.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-33.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-34.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-35.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-36.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-37.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-38.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-39.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/scalo-farini-40.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="design" /><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/scalo-farini-featured-image.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Exposed &amp;amp; Interlaced – Exploring Motion in Analog and Digital</title><link href="/2017/05/01/exposed-and-interlaced.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Exposed &amp; Interlaced – Exploring Motion in Analog and Digital" /><published>2017-05-01T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-05-01T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>/2017/05/01/exposed-and-interlaced</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/05/01/exposed-and-interlaced.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Exposed &amp;amp; Interlaced – Exploring Motion in Analog and Digital&lt;/em&gt; is a sequence of imaging chronicling a dance performance into 10 different fragments. The viewer will be able to view each fragment as a long exposure film print, as a representation of analog means, and an interactive lenticular that will allow the viewer to see a short video clip by changing their perspective, as a representation of digital means. The fragments will be displayed sequentially to communicate the entire dance performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/215510021&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Skip to &lt;a href=&quot;#diy-motion-lenticular-tutorial&quot;&gt;DIY Motion Lenticular Tutorial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conceptual-development&quot;&gt;Conceptual Development:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This idea was formed with my own experiences here at NYU Shanghai and also when I studied abroad. I took the Intro to Film Photography class in NYU Prague with the great artist/Professor Bara Mrazkova. I loved every second of the class and also the time I got to spend in the darkroom, the unexpected surprises along with the special personality of the film, and the delicate nuance. I also took a class with Professor Moon last semester at NYU Shanghai called Kinetic Interfaces, where I had the chance to experiment with Microsoft Kinect, a motion sensing device and the body movement data. For the final project of that class, I did a dance collaboration with my friend Ann. I was pretty amazed by how the human body was recognized and captured.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had this idea of doing human size photogram to show the human movement. According to Wikipedia, “a photogram is a photographic image made without a camera by placing objects directly onto the surface of a light-sensitive material such as photographic paper and then exposing it to light. The usual result is a negative shadow image that shows variations in tone that depends upon the transparency of the objects used. Areas of the paper that have received no light appear white; those exposed through transparent or semi-transparent objects appear gray” (&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Photogram&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Photogram&lt;/a&gt;). Then I found a photographic artist Floris Neusüss who did human size photograms (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.vonlintel.com/Floris-Neususs.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://www.vonlintel.com/Floris-Neususs.html&lt;/a&gt;). I contacted the gallery inquiring about the process and materials and I heard back from them with the answers I needed. However, given the fact that this idea has a really strict requirement on the space, a darkroom with enough space with a big enough pool/bathtub for developing prints, and also the materials, customized size/unusual big size photo papers, which would potentially elevate the cost of the project by a fairly large amount as well as the time consumption. I decided to pivot it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of analog media taking up the entire project, I thought it would be a good idea to bring digital into the field. Kinect can sense and record body motion data in digital form, and film photography is an analog way to record things. I started paying attention to the contrast and different between these two means. Although we live in an analog world, almost every single aspect has been heavily digitized. When you go to a concert, you see a wall of iPhones screen lit up; when you go to a museum, you see people with lenses capturing people striking poses with the art works; people read pdfs; etc. Almost all the analog media have at least one or multiple replacements that feature convenience on user’s side when it comes to distribution, utilization and manipulation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having dance as the as the content that shared by digital and analog approach of data recording, I started looking for media for presenting the data. AJ introduced lenticular and &lt;a href=&quot;https://gifpop.io&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;gifpop&lt;/a&gt; to me. Lenticular printing is a technology in which lenticular lenses (a technology that is also used for 3D displays) are used to produce printed images with an illusion of depth, or the ability to change or move as the image is viewed from different angles. I thought this would be a good way to present digital data which essentially is a short snippet of the dance piece and that data is in point-cloud form since digital recorded data can be easily modified and that directly shows how the Kinect device is sensing and selecting the samples, which is those dots where infrared light it emits lands. Same snippet of dance piece was also recorded on a long-exposed negative. After developing the negative, I printed it out with an enlarger onto a light-sensitive photo paper. Each fragment of the dance piece has two presentations with one being long-exposure film print and one being point cloud lenticular sheet, and in total 10 fragments will be displayed sequentially to communicate the entire dance performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea of this project is a culmination of my skill set as I am applying the film photography techniques I learned in Prague with the Kinect motion sensing skills I learned in IMA. A wholly original concept, this project dares to mix means of media that haven’t been mixed before and is an opportunity for me to contribute to the fields of work I have always admired in motion capture, film photography, and performance based art, while starting quality documentation in areas that have been ill documented, like lenticular printing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;technical-development&quot;&gt;Technical Development:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;lenticular-effects&quot;&gt;Lenticular Effects&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since I had experience with film photography before, I was pretty confident the analog output of this project would not be a challenge compared to making lenticular sheet. I started off with doing research on lenticular techniques. Here’s the general procedure I summarized: order lenticular sheet, pitch testing, interlace images, print, lamination (please go to the end of this post for a more detailed DIY lenticular tutorial). Lenticular technique has a couple of effects – flip, 3D, morph, and motion. Flip makes an image flip from one image to the next. 3D effect creates depth on a normally flat surface. The 3D Effect effect is generated by splicing several frames together to trick the viewer into seeing the 3D effect. Morph effects gradually change one image to another image through the use of sophisticated image algorithms. Motion effect uses multiple frames of an action to show movement from the beginning to the end. In my case, motion would be the effect I need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;pitch-test&quot;&gt;Pitch Test&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Making lenticular sheet relies heavily on a good printer. The school printer has the maximum of 1200 DPI. Lenticular sheet has one configuration which is LPI (lenticules per inch). Since the images have to be interlaced, the number of frames of images being used multiples LPI of the lenticular sheet should be no more than the maximum DPI of a printer. I started with purchasing lenticular sheets with a relatively low LPI, 25 and 32 from this &lt;a href=&quot;https://shop36592958.taobao.com/?spm=a1z10.1-c.0.0.rEmcSN&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;store&lt;/a&gt;. After I received them, I realized they might be too thick for a lenticular sheet, but it could be a good testing round. I did pitch testing, which is essentially a calibration tool. It calibrates the printer, media and lenticular sheet used for a particular image. The purpose of the pitch test is to determine which LPI pitch matches the particular printer/media/lenticular sheet combination. Since output devices may have slight differences in variability, pitch test is needed on each output device you intend to print interlaced images to. Shift your viewing angle left and right. Look at each bar and determine which bar gives you the widest flip from solid black to white across the entire width of the printed area. The bar that represents the best (widest) flip is the proper LPI that you need to interlace your files to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;25-32-50-70-75-100-lpi&quot;&gt;25, 32, 50, 70, 75, 100 LPI&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It turned out that the 32 LPI was actually 31.56 LPI. I decided to make a lenticular testing with a gif I found online to test the motion effect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
    25 LPI VS 32 LPI
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-4.gif&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
  GIF credit: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.creativeapplications.net/tutorials/how-to-create-interactive-loops-using-lenticular-animation-and-gifpop/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bryce Summers, CMU Undergraduate studying Computer Science&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It worked. Since its a low LPI lenticular lens, the interlace lines/gaps are pretty obvious though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;video_container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;video controls=&quot;controls&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot;&gt;
    &lt;source src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-5.m4v&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/video&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
	Bryce Summers’ GIF with a 32 LPI lenticular lens
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I purchased more to test out 50 70 75 100 LPI lenticular lens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
	50 LPI VS 70 LPI
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
	75 LPI VS 100 LPI
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Among these four, it was sort of impossible to figure out the pitch testing for 100. For 50, 70 and 75 LPI, the actual LPI I got was 50.17, 70.23 and 75.30.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video_container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;video controls=&quot;controls&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot;&gt;
    &lt;source src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-9.m4v&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/video&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
Bryce Summers’ GIF with a 70 LPI lenticular lens
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
25, 32, 50, 70, 75, 100 LPI
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
25, 32, 50, 70, 75, 100 LPI
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After taking into consideration the thickness, resolution, pitch test result and smoothness of the motion effect, I decided to go with 70 LPI lenticular lens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;point-cloud-vs-color&quot;&gt;Point Cloud VS Color&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video_container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;video controls=&quot;controls&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot;&gt;
    &lt;source src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-12.m4v&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/video&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was trying to decide what sort of data visualization to show on a lenticular print, and someone told to apply colors of the specific infrared landing points captured by the normal camera in Kinect. I decided t it a try the video above shows how it turned out. I didn’t continue with this for two reasons with first being it didn’t look good, and the second, point cloud represents the essential sampling step in digital data processing. If I had to show color, a better camera would actually give me a better imaging of the dance movement movie with better color and resolution. It makes more sense to show point cloud with a lenticular lens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;nyu-shanghai-default-printing-paper-vs-200g250g-laser-printing-paper&quot;&gt;NYU Shanghai Default Printing Paper VS 200g/250g Laser Printing Paper&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
	200 &amp;amp; 250g laser printing paper with NYU Shanghai 8F printer
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I tried to used different paper because based on my research, a better paper might make the effect smoother. However, the testing with 200g &amp;amp; 250g laser printing paper was a disaster. Although according to maximum of 300g paper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suspect that the ink wasn’t dry enough so it looked ruined. In normal cases, a high DPI ink printer would be better than a laser printer in lenticular printing. Thus I decided to stick with the NYU shanghai default printing paper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;black-point-cloud-vs-white-point-cloud&quot;&gt;Black Point Cloud VS White Point Cloud&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
	Black point cloud VS white point cloud
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video_container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;video controls=&quot;controls&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot;&gt;
    &lt;source src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-15.m4v&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/video&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
White point cloud on dark background
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video_container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;video controls=&quot;controls&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot;&gt;
    &lt;source src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-16.m4v&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/video&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
Black point cloud on white background
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;lamination&quot;&gt;Lamination&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The basic procedure is to laminate paper to adhesive and then laminate them to lenticular lens. When laminate adhesive, I peeled half off, and laminate, then do the other half, this can decrease the annoying bubbles that always appear in the lamination process. Please see this &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7lwu3EI1bF4&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;tutorial video&lt;/a&gt; for further instructions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;filming&quot;&gt;Filming&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kinect + film camera on a tripod. I took 20 long-exposure (half second only) photos with the film camera, while recording 20 snippets of the dance performance with each being 25 frames (only 15 was selected). Framerate of the program was around 30 fps, so 15 frames would match what the camera captured.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-17.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-18.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;developing-negatives-and-printing-photos&quot;&gt;Developing Negatives and Printing Photos&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After movement was recorded with both methods, I went to the DN Darkroom in M50 to develop my negatives and printed the photos out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-19.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-20.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-21.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-22.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-23.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
A sketch of unifying sizes of point cloud prints(A4), lenticular lenses(20cm*30cm), and light sensitive photopaper(9.5*12 inches)
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I decided to make the final size for both film photographs and lenticular prints to be 18*27cm which involved paper cutter and laser cutter(for lenticular lenses).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-24.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-25.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-26.gif&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
Kinect captured point cloud
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video_container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;video controls=&quot;controls&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot;&gt;
    &lt;source src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-27.m4v&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/video&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;acknowledgement&quot;&gt;Acknowledgement&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fespa.com/news/features/lenticular-printing-explained.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lenticular printing explained - part 1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.outeraspect.com/basic_lenticular_effects.php&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;LENTICULAR EFFECTS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.microlens.com/pages/pitch_test.htm&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;CREATING AND USING A PITCH TEST&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;www.3dmix.com/eng/download.php&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Leticular Software&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://content.photojojo.com/how-to-make-lenticular-images/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;4 Easy Steps To Making Old-Fashioned Lenticular Images From Your Photos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://triaxes.com/articles-on-technology/lenticular_motion/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Creating lenticular images with motion effect&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://dplenticular.com/technology/how-to-interlace-in-photoshop/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;How to interlace in Photoshop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would like to thank all the following people for helping with my Capstone Project:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Professors: Scott Fitzgerald, Anna Greenspan, Dan Mikesell, JH Moon, Sakar Pudasaini and Clay Shirky&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IMA Fellows:&lt;a href=&quot;http://ajlevine.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;AJ&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://godoymarcela.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Marcela&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kgrnbrg.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Kyle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dancer: Ann F. Yang&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://weibo.com/u/3002081872?topnav=1&amp;amp;wvr=6&amp;amp;topsug=1&amp;amp;is_all=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DN Film Club&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feedback and filming: &lt;a href=&quot;http://lewei.me/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Richard Lewei Huang&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://trhorick.github.io/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tyler Rhorick&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://sunjingyi.cc/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jingyi Sun&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://shop36592958.taobao.com/?spm=a1z10.1-c.0.0.rEmcSN&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;可可的唯一(Taobao vendor)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Funding support: NYU Shanghai Capstone Team&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;diy-motion-lenticular-tutorial&quot;&gt;&lt;a id=&quot;diy-motion-lenticular-tutorial&quot;&gt;DIY Motion Lenticular Tutorial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;order-lenticular-sheets&quot;&gt;Order Lenticular Sheets&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Lenticular sheets vary from 10LPI to more than 100LPI. Choose the correct LPI is the key step before making lenticular prints. Smaller LPI lenses have clear/obvious lines which can be distracting or make the image motion effect seem less smooth. 50-75 is a good range for motion lenticular. If the LPI above 75, a high DPI ink printer is recommended, and pitch testing is pretty difficult to conduct when you DIY.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Make sure: LPI * number of frames &amp;lt;= Highest DPI on your printer&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I order my lenticular sheets from &lt;a href=&quot;https://shop36592958.taobao.com/?spm=a1z10.1-c.0.0.FBpwnz&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;this place&lt;/a&gt;. Good/helpful service if you speak Chinese. They have a wide range of lenticular lens with different LPIs. The normal ones they sell is 20cm * 30cm, but you can choose the orientation of the lenticules. I picked horizontal lenticules (20cm) because my prints are vertical.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Make sure you buy their glue/adhesive sheet too&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I have 25, 32, 50, 70, 75, 100 six configurations with vertical/horizontal orientations, if you wanna experiment with them, feel free to come to me.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;pitch-testing&quot;&gt;Pitch Testing&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Just like some Taobao vendors, lenticular sheets they sell can not really be trusted as well. 25 LPI can actually be 25.23, and 75 LPI can actually be 75.123. Each lens LPI might vary even if you order them a bunch with the same configuration.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Pitch testing is REALLY REALLY IMPORTANT! An accurate pitch can make the motion effect more smooth.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.3dmix.com/eng/download.php&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;This is the place&lt;/a&gt; where I downloaded my pitch testing sheet generator. The Mac one didn’t work for me, so I had to use a PC/Wine on Mac to generate pitch testing sheet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-28.gif&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Three to four rounds of pitch testing is necessary for a lens to get as accurate as possible(ie. xx.xx). For example, for a 70 LPI lens, I would do 70.00-70.10,-70.20-…-72 first, then 70.00-70.03-70.06- … – 70.60, then 70.10-70.11-70.12- … – 70.30. For each round, the range is getting smaller, also the step is getting smaller too.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Make sure your print resolution matches your printer DPI.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Put the printed pitch test sheet under the lenticular screen. You can see the similar picture:&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-29.gif&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Close one eye and turn the head to the left, and then to the right. Look at the moire moving. Among the strips there are two strips where moire runs TOWARDS each other: the top moire moves from left to right, the bottom one moves from right to left (or otherwise). These two strips are close to the necessary strip.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The pitch of the strip that is the most continuous(fullest black or white) is close to the lenticular sheet pitch.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;interlacing-images-record-action-in-photoshop-recommended-for-mass-reproduction&quot;&gt;Interlacing Images (&lt;strong&gt;record action in photoshop recommended for mass reproduction&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;After pitch test, it is time to bring out the good ol’ pal, Photoshop&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Import video/gif, and convert them to frames&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-30.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Create a new file with final printing size(including bleed)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Set the resolution to be LPI x frames (in my case, 70.23 x 15 = 1053.45)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-31.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Select frames you need from the video/gif file&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Drag them onto the final printing file&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-32.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Scale and position those frames&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Make sure each frame is correctly positioned and the content is within the border&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-33.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8 Create a new file from the menu&amp;lt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Set the “Width” and “Height” to Y pixels (Y = the number of images you are interlacing, in my case 15 pixels x 15 pixels). Set the resolution to LPI x frames. In my case, 70.23 x 15 = 1053.45.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-34.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Zoom to the maximum and use the selection tool (“Marquee tool”), select one pixel line or column (&lt;strong&gt;horizontal is better for flip and vertical is mandatory for 3D, in my case horizontal line with one pixel height selected&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Fill this selection in black: in the menu bar go to: “Edit”–&amp;gt; ”Fill” and select “Black” from the “Content” dropdown menu&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Our “Pattern” is ready: “Select All”, in the menu; choose “Edit”–&amp;gt; “Define Pattern” and save this with a name like “xyz.xyz LPI xyz frames” In my case, “70.23LPI 15 frames”&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-35.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Go back to the final printing file, create a new layer and fill it with the pattern we just defined ”Select”–&amp;gt; ”All”&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Then in menu again: “Edit” –&amp;gt; ”Fill” for “Content” choose “Pattern” and choose the pattern you just made. This will fill the layer with the selected pattern&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-36.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Turn this grid into a selection: in the menu “Selection” –&amp;gt; “Color Range” select “Shadows”&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;This will select the black lines&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-37.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-38.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Go to your first “Layer”; in the menu “Layer” –&amp;gt; “Layer Mask” –&amp;gt; “Reveal Selection”&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;This will reveal the image information sitting behind the selection (in my case 1/15 of the image)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/exposed&amp;amp;interlaced-39.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Go back to your layer “pattern mask” and move it for one pixel (in my case, one pixel down) and repeat the previous step on the second image layer. (In my case, this will reveal 1/15 of the second frame, and filling 2/15 of the final printing image)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Repeat the previous step till the final printing image is filled with 1/(number of frames) (1/15 in my case) of each frame&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Flatten your result and it is ready to output/print&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;printing&quot;&gt;Printing&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Ink printer is recommended, and photopaper can make the effect look better.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Laser printer would work too, but paper options that are compatible are more limited. Ink might not be able to stay well on the paper.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;lamination-1&quot;&gt;Lamination&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/7lwu3EI1bF4&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="interactive-media" /><summary type="html">Exposed &amp;amp; Interlaced – Exploring Motion in Analog and Digital is a sequence of imaging chronicling a dance performance into 10 different fragments. The viewer will be able to view each fragment as a long exposure film print, as a representation of analog means, and an interactive lenticular that will allow the viewer to see a short video clip by changing their perspective, as a representation of digital means. The fragments will be displayed sequentially to communicate the entire dance performance.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/exposed-and-interlaced-featured-image.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Swing</title><link href="/2017/03/23/swing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Swing" /><published>2017-03-23T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2017-03-23T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/2017/03/23/swing</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/03/23/swing.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Swing&lt;/em&gt; is a new music interface installation featuring a swinging lattern with elastics. It soundifies locations, acceleration, and also elasticity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/210139899&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Filmed by Kinsa Durst&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edited by Zhang Zhan&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Swing&lt;/em&gt; is my final project for NIME class at NYU Shanghai. It is an update of my previous project, Balls, based on p5.js and a mobile device that has the built-in accelerometer. I wanted to this it a step further by replacing p5.js with MAX/Msp as the sound generating platform and adding another physical object to amplify the movement triggering aspect of the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this project, a phone is placed inside of the lantern with diecut pattern. The lantern is hung by an elastic string. The built-in accelerometer sends current X, Y, Z value to MAX/Msp patch via Open Sound Control. The patch triggers three different sounds with three separate gate/threshold on each of X, Y, Z data. Through this piece, I am trying to soundify the relative movement of an object with the intervention of elastic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/swing-12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="interactive-media" /><summary type="html">Swing is a new music interface installation featuring a swinging lattern with elastics. It soundifies locations, acceleration, and also elasticity.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/swing-featured-image.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">DISTANCE</title><link href="/2017/03/01/distance.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="DISTANCE" /><published>2017-03-01T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2017-03-01T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/2017/03/01/distance</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/03/01/distance.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;DISTANCE&lt;/em&gt; is inspired from a quote about the Moon and chinese poems I like where the Moon is romanticized as people’s beloved ones who are far away. In this project, users are able to get the distance between where they are and where their beloved ones are by entering two locations, and a visual comparison of their distance to the moon and the distance to the beloved ones will follow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Project Demo: &lt;a href=&quot;/distance/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DISTANCE&lt;/a&gt; (for a better experience, please open the link in Google Chrome)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is this quote that I heard of before and to be honest I don’t remember exact words-it is basically saying no matter how far apart two people are, compared to the distance between earth and moon, it is a lot easier for the two to meet than one of them going to the moon. This might sound ridiculous, however, this quote reminded me of the common approach that many ancient Chinese poets used to express that they were longing for faraway beloved in their masterpieces. It can be summarized as “though we are far apart, both looking at the moon, and it de facto makes us closer to each other”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is my basic basic wireframe sketch for the webpage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/distance-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the main ”DISTANCE” page, users need to type in two locations, and on click, google map javascript api will return the distance. Once the distance is received, it will show up next to the location input area along with a “COMPARE” button. The “COMPARE” button will lead you to the COMPARE page where you get to see two scaled lines according to the actual  of distance between moon and earth and the distance between two places users input earlier. The third page is a simple about-this-project page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/distance-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three buttons at the bottom of these three pages, about, distance, and my portfolio, so that users have to input locations and then go to compare page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/distance-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/distance-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Distance data is being passed to COMPARE page from DISTANCE/main page through “?d=xxxx” at the end of the URL.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used three.js and Google map javascript api in this project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;天涯咫尺 :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Credits:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/CoryG89/MoonDemo&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://github.com/CoryG89/MoonDemo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://aerotwist.com/tutorials/getting-started-with-three-js/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://aerotwist.com/tutorials/getting-started-with-three-js/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.howtojs.org/getting-started-with-three-js-3d-earth-part-ii/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://www.howtojs.org/getting-started-with-three-js-3d-earth-part-ii/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://learningthreejs.com/blog/2013/09/16/how-to-make-the-earth-in-webgl/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://learningthreejs.com/blog/2013/09/16/how-to-make-the-earth-in-webgl/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mattloftus.github.io/2016/02/03/threejs-p2/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://mattloftus.github.io/2016/02/03/threejs-p2/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="interactive-media" /><summary type="html">DISTANCE is inspired from a quote about the Moon and chinese poems I like where the Moon is romanticized as people’s beloved ones who are far away. In this project, users are able to get the distance between where they are and where their beloved ones are by entering two locations, and a visual comparison of their distance to the moon and the distance to the beloved ones will follow.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/distance-featured-image.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Thirstea</title><link href="/2016/12/12/thirstea.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Thirstea" /><published>2016-12-12T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2016-12-12T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/2016/12/12/thirstea</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2016/12/12/thirstea.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thirstea&lt;/em&gt; is a tea plant that feeds on the attention it gets on social media. The project is made up of a plant of tea tree and an irrigation system that is hooked to a Twitter bot and a webcam. The twitter bot will tweet about the growth of the plant every day with photos of the plant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/195745514&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Video filmed and edited by Zhang Zhan&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Project by Richard Lewei Huang and Zhang Zhan&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Music: Bon Iver - 8 (circle)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the number of new followers gained that day exceeds 3 – we opted to give the plant water for every single follower it gets. The program checks for new followers every 10 minutes, and runs the motor for 1 minute for each follower gained. In this way the program can be more responsive to changes on social media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We purchased a second-hand HP desktop computer at a seedy location near the Baoshan Rd electronics market with 139 kuai (20 dollars). To implement the idea we program the arduino to communicate with whatever it connects to via serial. On the computer side, we opted to use Python for its versatility and its wealth of libraries that are ready-to-use. We used Twython to communicate with Twitter, PySerial to talk with the Arduino with serial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Python sketch here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://pastebin.com/81TD8zd8&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://pastebin.com/81TD8zd8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We used an Android phone kindly donated by luis m-n as a webcam. The phone, equipped with IP Webcam app, serves a livestream from its IP address on the WiFi network. We connected the computer onto the same WiFi so that both can communicate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We built a rectangle frame to be placed on the ground, and one arm was installed vertically at one of the four corners to support another horizontal arm with a drilled hole at the end so that water tube could fit the hole and water can drip from right above the tea tree plant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We envision Thirstea as both a social commentary on the attention-seeking behaviour on social media and a social experiment to see how many followers we can get / how long the tree can live off social media attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/thirstea-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/thirstea-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/thirstea-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/thirstea-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/thirstea-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/thirstea-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/thirstea-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/thirstea-8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/thirstea-9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/thirstea-10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/thirstea-11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="interactive-media" /><summary type="html">Thirstea is a tea plant that feeds on the attention it gets on social media. The project is made up of a plant of tea tree and an irrigation system that is hooked to a Twitter bot and a webcam. The twitter bot will tweet about the growth of the plant every day with photos of the plant.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/thirstea-featured-image.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Above The Sea</title><link href="/2016/12/12/above-the-sea.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Above The Sea" /><published>2016-12-12T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2016-12-12T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/2016/12/12/above-the-sea</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2016/12/12/above-the-sea.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Above The Sea&lt;/em&gt; translates weather forecast data(sea level and main weather condition) of a certain city into notes and chords and visualizes the data in a column system in p5. After being laser cut onto the clear acrylic board, the songs about the sea level and weather above the sea can be played on a record player. This project tranforms and stores weather data in an analog way, providing a new musical interface for data-human interaction with an artistic approach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Project Demo: &lt;a href=&quot;/p5-above-the-sea/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Above The Sea – Shanghai&lt;/a&gt; (for a better experience, please open the link in Google Chrome)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/195638313&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/195638313&quot;&gt;Above The Sea&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/user36907083&quot;&gt;Zhang Zhan&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com&quot;&gt;Vimeo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Video filmed and editted by Zhang Zhan&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Music: Bon Iver - 666 ʇ&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This projects gets weather forecast data from the 5 day/3 hour forecast API from &lt;a href=&quot;http://openweathermap.org/api&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;OpenWeatherMap&lt;/a&gt;. Since the minimum unit of the data interval is 3 hours, the API gives me about 35-40 pairs of the sea level and main weather condition data. Each 3 hour interval represents one bar, and each bar has 8 beats of notes in membrane synth in one chord with a certain arrangement that represent main weather condition in that interval. There’s also a longer note created in FM synth representing the sea level. The API is live, which means it gets updated every 10 minutes(this interval is set in P5 so it can be changed easily).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With my professor Luisa’s help, I decided to map 4 main weather conditions received from the weather forecast API with notes in 4 different chords.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clear – C major&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clouds – C minor&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rain – A minor&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Snow – B minor&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sea level data aka the long note that lasts through one bar is mapped into a scale of C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5 note.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to preserve the songs, I opted to include &lt;a href=&quot;http://instructables.com/id/Laser-Cut-Record/?ALLSTEPS&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;laser cut records&lt;/a&gt; as part of the project since the idea itself is really fascinating and you can play it back anytime you want. I needed to record the piece first and then run it through the python program and processing sketch provided by the instructables post. However, I had to make some modifications such as the size of the records, the radius of the most inner grove, rpm, maximum size of the pdf files(since one song’s groves on one pdf will be way too much to be imported into illustrator, so I had to split them into 9 pdfs and then import them so that no groves will be missing.) I bought a record player on Taobao–230kuai–the cheapest but legitimate one I could find. I then did testing with a random song in three settings suggested by the post–frequency 5000, speed 100, dpi 1200, and power 12, 20 and 24. It turns out that power 20 one sounds the best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I laser cut three music pieces I recorded on Dec 6 of three cities–New York, Prague, and Shanghai–where I lived since last year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/above-the-sea-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/above-the-sea-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/above-the-sea-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/above-the-sea-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/above-the-sea-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/above-the-sea-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/above-the-sea-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the laser cut process was done, I washed those three records with water and soap to get rid of all the tiny dust from the cutting processing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/above-the-sea-8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/above-the-sea-9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listen to the result in the video. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/above-the-sea-10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/above-the-sea-11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/above-the-sea-12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="interactive-media" /><summary type="html">Above The Sea translates weather forecast data(sea level and main weather condition) of a certain city into notes and chords and visualizes the data in a column system in p5. After being laser cut onto the clear acrylic board, the songs about the sea level and weather above the sea can be played on a record player. This project tranforms and stores weather data in an analog way, providing a new musical interface for data-human interaction with an artistic approach.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/above-the-sea-featured-image.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">A Song Without Words</title><link href="/2016/12/12/a-song-without-words.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Song Without Words" /><published>2016-12-12T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2016-12-12T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/2016/12/12/a-song-without-words</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2016/12/12/a-song-without-words.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Song Without Words&lt;/em&gt; is an interactive dance piece using Kinect with projection of visuals created according to the body movement sensed by Kinect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/195400876&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dancer and choreographer: Ann Yang&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Music: Sandy Lam - 无言歌&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Filmed by Jingyi Sun, Maggie Walsh and Zhang Zhan&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edited by Zhang Zhan&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This dance piece is a visual response to the song, 无言歌, by Sandy Lam. My friend, Ann Yang, a talented dancer, choreographed this dance under my general guideline. There are four stages in the dance performance–birth, accumulation, explosion, and decay. Each stage is represented by different visual effects such as point cloud, particle explosion system, particle ring, and particles collapsing. The main point cloud figure is the live visual resemblance of the dancer, and the dancer also react to the visuals by modifying her dance routines based on what the visual is created by her previous movements and positions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/a-song-without-words-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/a-song-without-words-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;calibration&quot;&gt;Calibration&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Set up Kinect and adjust its detection range to get the best detection with proper depth of the dancer&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Open Processing sketch to project a solid color image to the wall, and adjust projection area in Resolume to fully cover the area&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/a-song-without-words-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/a-song-without-words-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;phase-i---birth&quot;&gt;Phase I - Birth&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Dancer rises from the floor&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Particles gather and form a ring around the dancer&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/a-song-without-words-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/a-song-without-words-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;phase-ii---accumulation&quot;&gt;Phase II - Accumulation&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Dancer’s point cloud image appears&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Point cloud image starts rotating in the virtual space and the dancer starts dancing to the point cloud image based on the location&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;More particles start falling from the point cloud image&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/a-song-without-words-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/a-song-without-words-8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;phase-iii---explosion&quot;&gt;Phase III - Explosion&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Particles stops falling&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;More randomly allocated particles appear on the surface still&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Whenever dancer’s closest point(usually foot or hand) hits a group of particles, those particles bounce off immediately at a high speed to create chaos and massive movements&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/a-song-without-words-9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/a-song-without-words-10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;phase-iv---decay&quot;&gt;Phase IV - Decay&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Bouncing particles fade away&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Dancer get closer to the floor with more floor movements&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;New particles move across the screen from the bottom at a even higher speed to create falling illusion&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Dancer lies down while raising hand acting as falling&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Background slightly brightens, and becomes solid white in the end&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Dancer lies on the floor still&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/a-song-without-words-11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/a-song-without-words-12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/a-song-without-words-13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to Prof. JH Moon for letting me use his Mac Pro, keyboard, track pad, his screen, and the speaker. The visuals are created in a processing sketch with a control panel. Visuals are sent to Arena with syphon, but the control panel is not sent to the Arena so that I can do live control including particle speed, color gradience, transition over the visuals. A Kinect is used to sense the depth and capture the shape of the object within the sensing range. The explosion and particles is attracted by the closest point within the sensing area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Special thanks to Prof. JH Moon, Jingyi Sun and Maggie Walsh.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="interactive-media" /><summary type="html">A Song Without Words is an interactive dance piece using Kinect with projection of visuals created according to the body movement sensed by Kinect.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/a-song-without-words-featured-image.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Shy Mirror</title><link href="/2016/12/05/shy-mirror.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shy Mirror" /><published>2016-12-05T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2016-12-05T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/2016/12/05/shy-mirror</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2016/12/05/shy-mirror.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Shy Mirror&lt;/em&gt; is an interactive installation created by Alexis Zerafa, Xiran Yang, and me. We wanted to explore human nature as it pertains to vanity. It is easy to become infatuated with self-reflection, to a point where one becomes obsessed with the reflection of the self. Our project attempts the fracture that infatuation, by designing a mirror that spins away when a viewer approaches it. This forces the person attempting to view themselves to instead view others around them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/194319808&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Filmed by Alexis Zerafa, Xiran Yang and Zhang Zhan&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edited by Alexis Zerafa&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project focuses on the narcissistic behaviors shared by common human beings. We would like to raise the participant’s self-awareness of narcissism by angling the mirror that people tend to walk up to and where they look at themselves. This action disables them from looking at themselves in the mirror and, instead, participants are forced to look at the reflection of others in the room. We like this idea because not only is the concept persuasive and easy to convey, but also the physical object is simplistic and relevant to a broad audience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The interaction part of the project is as simple as the concept–an infrared range finder and a stepper motor are connected to an Arduino Uno (a micro controller). Once the reading of the infrared range finder is smaller than the threshold we set according to many rounds of testing, which means an object is detected within the searching range, the Arduino Uno will tell the attached stepper motor to rotate 90 degrees. Once the reading of the infrared becomes bigger than the threshold, it means no more objects can be detected within the searching range, so the mirror would reset to the initial position as the reverse process after given the command to do so from the Arduino Uno. Participants are not required to actively interact with any electronic components; they need only get closer to the mirror. We would like the action to happen instinctively with very limited guidance, and in this way, the result–rotation of the mirror– triggered by the action would enhance the overall experience since it is unpredictable and, therefore, surprising.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A wood box frame(40x100cm) covered with white fabric functions as the base of the entire project, inside which the circuit hides. A thin but strong wood board drilled onto the fours legs of the wood box is the top of the box, and the stepper motor is placed in the center of the top with four screws drilled through the board and into the four mounting holes in the motor. Only the raft sticks out of the top of the box and the motor body is underneath the top hidden behind the white fabric.The mirror, a 2mm acrylic board(40x100cm) with a mirror-like reflective surface that has a wood frame in the back, is hanging from the top part of a bigger frame that stands on the box so that there is no weight resting on the raft. A small wood piece sticks out from the bottom of the mirror frame and touch nearly half of the raft. A paper clip and some clear tape are used to tie the raft and the small wood piece so they do not slip, and the stepper motor can rotate the mirror smoothly. The infrared range finder is installed on the top wood bar that is facing the participants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project is truly portable and easily reassembled due to the use of screws and lumber. It needs one socket nearby to power the circuit. We placed the project in a way that it was facing a white wall. Therefore the space in front of the range finder could be less crowded with a more still and pure background, which would definitely maintain the performance of the sensor at a good level. Even though the infrared range finder works well with normal room light, the room where Shy Mirror is exhibited should have as little bright sunlight as possible since sunlight would decrease the accuracy of the range finder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/shy-mirror-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/shy-mirror-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/shy-mirror-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/shy-mirror-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/shy-mirror-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/shy-mirror-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/shy-mirror-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/shy-mirror-8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/shy-mirror-9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/shy-mirror-10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/shy-mirror-11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photo credits: Xiran Yang
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/shy-mirror-12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/shy-mirror-13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/shy-mirror-14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/shy-mirror-15.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="interactive-media" /><summary type="html">Shy Mirror is an interactive installation created by Alexis Zerafa, Xiran Yang, and me. We wanted to explore human nature as it pertains to vanity. It is easy to become infatuated with self-reflection, to a point where one becomes obsessed with the reflection of the self. Our project attempts the fracture that infatuation, by designing a mirror that spins away when a viewer approaches it. This forces the person attempting to view themselves to instead view others around them.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/shy-mirror-featured-image.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Little Brothers Entertainment Brochure</title><link href="/2016/10/20/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Little Brothers Entertainment Brochure" /><published>2016-10-20T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2016-10-20T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>/2016/10/20/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2016/10/20/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure.html">&lt;p&gt;Company overview brochure design for Little Brothers Entertainment based in Shanghai.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure-8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure-9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure-10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure-11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure-12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure-13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure-14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure-15.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure-16.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure-17.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="design" /><summary type="html">Company overview brochure design for Little Brothers Entertainment based in Shanghai.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/little-brothers-entertainment-brochure-featured-image.jpg" /></entry></feed>